dextronet.com 2017-06-06

# Dextronet Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Back

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. You retain rights to all your information and data.

Your credit card information is used by our BMT Micro ecommerce partner only to process your order and it is not stored in any way and never viewed by us or available to us.

## The Information We Collect

We collect only the necessary contact information when you contact us and personal information provided by you when you purchase a product from us.

We use cookies to ensure you get the best user experience from the website. If you continue using this website, we assume that you consent to receiving all cookies on this website.

## The Way We Use Information

We do not share your personal information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete your order.

The information provided by you is used only to process your order and/or to inform you about new products and product updates. You can opt-out from these email updates.

We might use non-identifying and aggregate information, to better design our website and products.

When you contact us, we might use a part of the email message in our promotion materials as a testimonial, without publishing your full name. You have to right to decline any such use and we will promptly remove any such materials in 24 hours after your written request.

We reserve the right to publish the name and logo of your company in the list of our customers. We will promptly remove the name of your company in 24 hours after your written request.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

## Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

You can access or correct all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by contacting us.

## Our physical address

Our physical address is:

Jiri Novotny  
Boreticka 6  
62800 Brno  
Czech Republic

## How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us via our support form.
